Welcome back!
Clearly in a different environment, as you can probably tell.
And if you're new here, it's not New York City anymore.
We're back home in Chicago, where I was born and raised.
Today's video is gonna be a little different than my usual vlog.
Considering it's the end of the year, I thought I would sit down and show
you guys all my favorite things that I have discovered or used continuously all throughout
2024.
These are things that I have repurchased time and time again because of how much
I love it and cannot live without it.
I'm gonna break it down into categories.
We're gonna start off with beauty.
So we're gonna do skincare We're gonna do makeup haircare a few of my favorite
books that I've read as well as miscellaneous So anything that doesn't fall into the
previous category, so let's just get right into it I'm not gonna mumble any further
because I'm really excited I want to preface by saying I like to think of
myself as a minimalist as an I like to try new things But if I
find something that works for me I stick to it So everything that I'm showing
you guys I truly love and have been loving this is like my favorites list
solidified All right, let's start off with skincare now if you guys have been watching
me for a few months now You know that I've been struggling with acne before
I broke out this year I had glass skin But I have a few products
that have been with me since my clear skin days or my worst breakout and
that are still with Me now so the first product I want to mention is
castor oil.
I discovered this this year I knew before that it was good for your hair
growth for lashes brows But I only discovered that castor oil is actually such a
good skincare ingredient because it's super anti-inflammatory anti-inflammatory.
So when you have these breakouts, castor oil can act kind of, first of all,
it can repair your skin barrier, which is huge in terms of dealing with breakouts,
I also discovered.
And because it's anti-inflammatory, it helps with any acne or pimples.
Let me just tell you, it works miracles.
I take two, three drops every single night, mix it in with my favorite moisturizer,
and lather my face in it.
I've seen pimples go away because of this.
I've tried other pimple quick fixes.
Nothing beats castor oil.
Even if you don't have acne, I highly recommend, especially for the wintertime, if your
skin's a little bit drier, Just, okay?
Castor oil.
She's my baby, and I think I'll be using it for the rest of my
life.
And always make sure it's certified organic, it's cold-pressed, and that it's in a glass
bottle, okay?
Because otherwise, it's not true castor oil, from what I understand.
Next, this is the Caudalie Vinyl Perfect Brightening Dark Spot Serum.
I used this towards the end of my first major breakout of the year.
I noticed a huge difference as soon as my acne started to go away, and
I was just really dealing with hyperpigmentation.
She was my savior.
It also like smells really fresh.
The bottle instructs you to use it both morning and evening I just use it
in the morning and it makes your makeup look So so good Even if you
aren't wearing makeup your skin will look a bajillion times better just because of this
in addition to the Caudalie serum This is my tried-and-true product for so long now.
I've been using the serum probably For three years now and I still love it
so much.
This is the La Roche-Posay hyaluronic acid the b5 serum another beautiful product to use
on its own nothing else underneath your makeup you will look like a glowing goddess
okay i'm not wearing it right now but just trust and it always like refreshes
my skin so well i think i've been through over a dozen so just try
it okay i've tried other hyaluronic acid serums from different brands i will always always
come back to the lower ship of same one that's it next i used to
be a micellar water and cotton round girly when i would take off my makeup
that's what I would use but I found it to be really harsh on my
skin.
I feel like I was really aggressive.
It wasn't doing it for me.
I discovered these.
I bought these on Amazon.
They came in a 12 pack and they're these microfiber makeup removing towels.
I literally just take it, run it under the faucet under some like hot or
warm water.
I use it to wipe off my makeup after I apply jojoba oil.
I don't use micellar water anymore and it is amazing.
I feel like my skin has highly improved because of this.
It's less dried out.
When I take off my makeup I used to find that taking off my makeup
with micellar water just really dried it out.
Not anymore.
And these are super soft and gentle on your skin.
So I highly recommend.
Okay, next up.
I deal with terribly, terribly dry hands in the winter.
It's a yearly occurrence and it really sucks.
If you have a Trader Joe's near you, please run and get you the ultra
moisturizing hand cream, especially if you struggle with super dry hands like me or just
dry skin in general.
I've tried so many different hand creams and lotions and potions and Vaseline, Aquaphor.
Nothing beats how amazing this is.
This is something that my family has used for years.
My sister used to have really dry hands when she was a child.
So this has been something that my family and I have been using for years
on end.
This year specifically, I think I like really fell in love with it because in
my New York apartment, I have like four of these empty tubes sitting in my
nightstand drawer.
There was like a pumpkin spice scent.
It was a guava scent that I have.
This is the original.
I just love it.
It actually works wonders on my hands.
I applied it before I started filming.
I'm not sure if this qualifies as skincare or makeup, but I'm going to include
it in the skincare portion, or I guess the like self-care portion.
This is the UK Lash Eyelash Serum.
I've tried other eyelash serums before.
I like to try a lot of different products, and then when I find something,
I really stick to it, and I can say that I will not be steering
from my UK Lash.
I'm already on my second tube after taking a long long break i don't recommend
using lash serums continuously give your lashes a break especially if they have grown out
i've tried the grande lash found that was insanely irritating this is not irritating and
it actually makes your lashes grow out evenly i found with other lash serums my
lashes would grow like in super weird lengths not equal at all it just i
looked a mess this actually does a good job let's talk spf because spf is
so so incredibly important this This is something that's a recent addition, but I can
confidently say that it will be staying in my routine for a long time.
This is the ILIA Super Serum Skin Tint with SPF 40.
I highly recommend everyone to use SPF even in the wintertime.
Don't stay away from it, okay?
You'll thank me later.
This has niacinamide squalane and hyaluronic acid.
You won't need foundation.
You won't need concealer.
You can just walk out with this.
Half the time, that's what I do.
I just slather this on my face.
It looks like I have full coverage makeup while still having super glowy skin.
I'm just, I'm in love with it, and I love anything that provides a good
sunscreen protection because we want to have beautiful skin for the rest of our lives,
don't we?
This is something I don't think I've ever seen anybody talk about.
This is the Polite Society B.I.G.
Big Mouth Lip Plumping Oil Gloss.
I discovered this randomly at Ulta one time and I fell in love.
This actually works insanely well and it stings really bad initially.
It's just a clear gloss but it works wonderfully.
I'm huge on lip products and that is something that I just I love so
much.
I just repurchased recently, literally like two days ago.
Next up is the Kosas Revealer Concealer.
I love this stuff so much.
It also has hyaluronic acid in it.
I think that's my favorite skincare ingredient if you haven't, you know, picked up on
that already.
It is so creamy, so smooth without it being like super thick and heavy.
It still does a really good job at concealing whatever you want to conceal or
just brightening up your face, whatever it may be.
So this is the only concealer I used this entire year.
I just kept repurchasing over and over again.
My lips are currently stinging by the way.
They're stinging, they're burning, It's doing its job then also for foundation.
I never used to be a foundation girl I just was like terrified of it
for some reason like I felt like I couldn't find something that I actually really
loved my mom Helped me pick out this in New York when I went for
the first time with her this year I have not purchased any other foundation or
used any other foundation since this is the Dior backstage base and body foundation such
a perfect Consistency I love when makeup feels a little bit like skincare as and
it's not just like heavy makeup and it makes your skin look look natural and
glowy and beautiful while still providing coverage if you want it.
I love it so much.
I'm currently wearing it right now.
It's flawless.
I love it.
I just, I have no other way to describe it besides beautiful, gorgeous, stunning.
So if you're looking for a new foundation, I highly recommend you guys trying.
Again, super lightweight, but still good coverage.
It never leaves me feeling cakey or flaky or dry.
And that's something I used to think about foundation all the time.
And now I don't.
She's changed my mind.
Next up, this is something that's a little bit more of a recent addition to
my routine, but I am also in love with.
This is the makeup I Mario Soft Sculpt Transforming Skin Enhancer.
This is in the shade Light Medium.
I am a bronzer over contour girl all day every day and this is what
I recently am obsessed with.
It is like the creamiest but so subtle.
Like look at that.
It is just beautiful.
It blends into the skin so nicely, so seamlessly and it always gives me like
a natural bronze that's clearly still evident and shows on my face.
I love this product so much.
Lastly for makeup, I only have one with me right now because I'm home, but
it is the NYX Professional Makeup Lip Liners.
I'm obsessed with these.
This one is in the shade Nutmeg, and when I find a lip combo that
I'm obsessed with, it always involves one of the NYX lip liners.
This is the shade Nutmeg, and I've been using this a lot recently with my
road lip tint that I got in the shade Cinnamon Roll, which is like a
brown, shimmery lip gloss.
Such a beautiful, warm, spicy brown lip liner.
My other favorite NYX lip liner is my Tried and True Mahogany.
That is the shade name and it is so gorgeous.
I usually pair it with my Dior Lip Oil, which is also in the shade
Mahogany.
It is the perfect lip combination.
It's like more of a dark berry.
Obsessed with that lip liner.
I've put so many of my friends on it.
My sister, my best friend, my other girlfriends.
Everybody loves it.
I feel like it's a good universal shade, so definitely check out the shade Mahogany
if you want to know my like go-to lip combo.
All right, let's move into hair care these products.
This is my go-to routine This right here is all I will ever need I
think for the rest of my life Let's start off with hair oil the best
hair oil to exist ever.
This is the karistas elixir ultime hair oil It's literally it's done for she's empty.
There's nothing left I've been through so many of these tiny little bottles because I
love to buy my products in travel sizes It's like not too thick.
It's not too thin.
It always gives a nice beautiful shine obsessed with this I use it dry hair
wet hair before styling after styling you name it and it smells smells divine next
up the living proof flex Hairspray this apparently has heat protection, which I only recently
read on the bottle if you're looking for a hairspray That is not sticky or
too stiff leaving your hair feeling kind of gross.
This is the one for you I think it's on the name flex hairspray love
living proof so much I also love their dry shampoo, but this is something that
I always always use I have naturally curly hair But I've been straightening my hair
a lot blowing it out a lot and I find that this hairspray works so
beautifully on heat styled Hairstyles speaking of heat styling one product I cannot live without
and you guys have probably heard of so many times is the color wow dream
coat I get the extra strength version.
I'm not really sure why i've used the original strength But I find like the
more the more strength the better, you know what i'm saying?
Like okay less frizz sign me up sign me up I have seen my hair
heat styled before without using this product.
There is such a difference you guys don't even understand.
This really provides this like anti-frizz, anti-humidity, beautiful sleek hairstyle that every girl wants.
It's literally just achieved through this product and maybe a little bit of the Kerastase
hair oil in addition.
It's like blinding you guys, I'm so sorry.
But I'm obsessed with this.
I've been through an insane amount of bottles of this.
I've been through many sizes, the original size, obsessed.
I've even tried the curly hair one, but nothing beats this baby.
Love her.
For hair gel, anytime that I do slick backs or if I go to the
gym and want my hair to be out of my face and slicked away or
I just have like really annoying baby hairs.
Crown Affair Finishing Gel.
It smells so good you don't even understand.
I discovered this at the beginning of the year and this is the same bottle
from like January and it's only now about to like run out.
You don't even need to use that much I find and it's super lightweight.
I don't like super heavy gels on my hair and I find that this is
like the best product I found for that and it provides a really nice beautiful
sleek hairstyle slash look.
Then for pre-wash treatments and growing my hair and keeping my hair healthy.
I love rosemary oil.
I highly recommend this.
It's a Miel rosemary mint scalp and hair strengthening oil.
I do this part of my pre-wash hair oiling routine to grow my hair and
to have a healthier scalp.
I've heard so many people talk about it and it's for a good reason.
It's an amazing hair oil.
I've put my mom on this.
I've put my sister on this and I've actually noticed a difference in my hair
strength and growth.
You have to be consistent with it.
It's not going to be like your hair grows three inches overnight.
I wish that was the case, but it does work.
So highly recommend.
Lastly, another product I've put my mom and my sister on is the Lush Super
Milk.
I was influenced by Leah from Love Island.
If you guys know, that's how this product basically blew up and it smells.
Oh my God.
If you want to walk around being complimented that you smell delicious, this is all
you need.
This is all you need.
Like I can't even,
it's like sweet, but not so much that you're like gagging.
You know what I'm saying?
It's like a little coconutty, brown sugary, I would say a little bit of lemon.
It's like refreshing and sweet and yummy.
Like you can't get enough.
And it actually makes your hair really soft too.
So I apply this on wet hair.
You walk around turning heads because of how good it smells.
I'm not kidding.
That wraps up hair.
I think that wraps up all of beauty.
Let's dive a little bit now into books that I've read in 2024.
I didn't read as many books as I wish I did, but that's okay.
We always have next year.
And I did read a good amount to tell you guys my favorites.
I'm going to start off with the books I actually have with me to show
you guys.
These fall under the spiritual slash, I guess you could say self-growth, self-help genre.
I am huge on manifesting.
I love reading books surrounding that topic, anything that can kind of like clear up
the process even more because it can- there's so much information online and I feel
like it can get a little confusing or overwhelming and there's like so many different
things you have to do.
Not really.
So these two books I found helped simplify the process and really explain what manifesting
is and how you can do it.
This is the first book I read on manifesting this year and I think I'm
gonna reread it soon because it was so so good.
It's Manifest Seven Steps to Living Your Best Life by Roxie Nafusi, my mom gave
this to me.
She does such a good job at explaining how to manifest, how to persist, and
it kind of gives you like actionable steps, so it's not just giving you a
bunch of like random information, it tells you like what you can do, you know,
you have to cultivate self-love, practice gratitude, take action, like things like that, and then
she also gives her personal stories.
So I really loved it, it was such an easy, pleasurable read, it wasn't like
too much heavy information thrown at your face, and it was also really inspiring, so
I really loved it.
I also think it's quite a cute coffee table book.
And then this, this is The Universe Has Your Back by Gabrielle Bernstein.
She goes through her own personal journey, how she was battling severe drug and alcohol
addiction, and how she thought she would never get past it.
She tells the story of her personal life and how she got into her own
spiritual journey and eventually found success and like true inner peace and joy and love
within her life.
I'm kind of just like going off the back of my head because I don't
remember.
I read these at the beginning of the year, but I just remember being so
impacted by them.
She talked a lot about synchronicities and just seeing that around you and understanding that
things are working out for you And this book helped me so much through the
time that I was apartment hunting with my dad If you guys know like the
story my move to new york and that it was not easy at all This
book really helped me kind of just like stand my ground and understand and trust
that everything was going to be okay So it helped a lot with like my
anxiety surrounding it and just other things in life I think this is such a
nice beautiful beautiful book to read I highly recommend if you guys are interested in
those type of things If not, I also read quite a few fiction books just
for like pleasure and fun this year.
My first favorite was Everything I Know About Love by Dolly Alderton.
I think that is the perfect book for any girl in her 20s to read
or like late teens, early teens.
It doesn't really matter.
I think even like as an older woman, it's just such a beautiful book and
she kind of just goes through her life living in England and all the different
stages that I feel like basically every girl kind of goes through and just navigating
like love, relationships, friendships it's just such a funny story of someone's life but it's
also so beautiful and it was such a good read i devoured it i absolutely
loved it and then the second book that i also really loved was girl by
camille lawrence that was about a girl who grew up in france in i believe
like the 1940s and it was just taking you through her life her experiences as
a girl especially in a society in a time where they see girls as less
than and not as valuable i guess you could say i was also just really
attached to the character and her way of thinking and her way of storytelling you're
living her life through her eyes which I really loved and I also love that
it was set in France I don't know why I'm so attracted to books like
that I'm terrible at explaining books I cannot for the life of me I've said
this before but those were two books fiction wise that I really really love okay
now let's go quickly into clothing slash jewelry I've gotten questions about my silver hoops
that I wear over and over again these are from Nordstrom Rack I've repurchased I
think this is like my second pair because I lost my original pair but I
love these so much.
It's just from the Nordstrom Rack brand.
It's not like a specific brand sold at Nordstrom Rack.
The tag is just exactly that Nordstrom Rack.
I love them.
They're just like my go-to everyday staple silver hoops and I also love these bangles
from Hay Harper.
What I love about them is that they're waterproof.
I've worn these on vacation and water before in pools and at the beach.
I believe they're called the Rachel bangles and I think they're just such a chic
little everyday jewelry.
I wear these basically every single day.
If I'm wearing bracelets, I'm wearing these bangles.
So I love those for jewelry.
Now for clothing, I discovered these at the beginning of the summer.
I'd like to say I was early to the trend because I think they blew
up like shortly after on TikTok or something like that.
It's the garage tank tops.
I think this is the first one I bought.
These are the most perfect basic tank tops ever.
They suck you in and they're so comfortable.
I literally just wear them on their own sometimes or underneath.
They're absolutely perfect.
I bought another one in white because you can never I guess have too many
I don't know and then I recently got this one in black.
I love them so much.
They're so flattering on they're only I believe $22 and people say that they're exactly
like the tank air tank tops that are also super like loved but around $70 So
highly recommend these I love them so much I wear them a little bit too
often but bang for my buck and staying on the topic of basics This is
something i've had for the past year and a half and i've repurchased This is
the Skims Cotton Jersey Long Sleeve.
I get mine in the size extra small.
It is the most comfortable top I could ever own, especially for the wintertime.
This is something that I often layer underneath my sweaters because it's just like an
extra source of warmth.
That's the fun thing about basics.
You can wear it on its own.
You can wear it with something else.
It's like the perfect long sleeve.
That's all I can say about it.
So that's what I love for clothing and jewelry.
Now let's move on to our last section of miscellaneous items.
Bear with me.
We're almost through.
I've gotten questions before on how I make my matcha and I will show you
guys a more in-depth tutorial But this is the matcha that I use.
It's the naoki fine Japanese matcha.
I get this from Amazon I've tried a few different matcha brands before like ceremonial
gray I've even bought matcha in Japan like in Kyoto, Japan, but this is my
favorite one.
I don't know I just keep coming back to it.
I love it so much.
I love it's a tiny little pouch I find like the little tin cans just
run through really quickly This is around the same price as the tin cans, but
I think yeah, definitely more it just tastes good to me I don't know love
this matcha so highly recommend if you guys are looking for any matcha recommendations then
for tea I became a tea addict this year and I used to hate tea.
I never really liked it I thought it was just like boring I don't know
and the one tea that I have become obsessed with is the dandelion chai probiotic
tea I can never find it in store and sometimes not even on Amazon.
It's literally just tea Like why would I gatekeep tea like that's stupid.
I can never find it So when I do, I love it.
I became obsessed with dandelion leaf and root tea when I first broke out this
year.
I drank like four cups a day.
A day, religiously.
And I actually noticed such a big difference in my skin.
It has anti-inflammatory properties, skin health properties.
It also helps a lot with liver and kidney health.
Now, I just drink it for pure pleasure.
I don't really like the actual taste of dandelion root tea.
I find it a little bitter.
So when I discovered this, it was like music to my ears because it tastes
like chai.
It's a little bit cinnamony a little bit spicy so comforting so warming and it
also really helps after I eat if I ever feel Like super bloated or anything.
This one has like probiotic and it literally says supports healthy digestion I make two
cups of this basically every single night It's just in a big mug two cups
of water two tea bags my little nighttime ritual Love this tea and then I've
also talked about this multiple times before it is the five minute journal by intelligent
change I've been doing this for so many years now.
I just recently bought a new one I fill it out every morning and every
evening when I wake up when I go to sleep and it always has a
little quote What's crazy is that there's been mornings where I wake up.
I read the quote and i'm like, how is that?
Relating exactly to how i'm feeling this morning or to what i've been going through
recently and why is that exactly what I needed To hear so I love that.
It's like a little synchronicity that I I don't know I appreciate and it just
helps you start off your day beautifully by writing three things you're grateful for what
would make today great So I always write like maybe something that I want to
happen or if I know I have a plan later I write down how I
would like it to go usually comes true and then I have a daily affirmation
that you can write and Then you reflect on your day highlights of your day.
I love reflecting on like what went well every day It's just fun to kind
of feel like oh that was a good day.
It was a good day And then what did I learn today?
So it's just such a good everyday ritual to have and to be in tune
with myself with yourself kind of random But I cannot sleep without a sleep mask
I sleep like a baby with one and this is from the brand slip Specifically
my mom got this for me and my sister each last christmas and I am
obsessed with it It's a silk sleep mask and I just I love it so
so much I've had other ones but this one is specific because it's like silk
and like it's a cutesy little champagne Color so I cannot sleep without a sleep
mask.
In fact, I kind of look psycho and then I have a silk bonnet to
like Protect my hair.
I look crazy.
I look crazy at night, but you know what?
It's all for a good reason And then lastly this is kind of just like
my little personality trait.
I don't know why I just feel so chic with it It's a Chanel compact
beauty mirror.
I love just being like this.
No, not actually.
That would be like kind of crazy.
But I keep this in all of my bags.
Like I always make sure to transfer it between bags whenever I leave the house.
Always have it on me.
Apply my lip liner.
Whatever it may be.
And I just feel so elevated and chic and feminine and cute and girly with
this.
So this is just like a personal little favor.
It's not something I would say is necessary.
But I love her.
So I thought I should include her.
I think that concludes everything.
If you actually made it through this entire video and watched all of my favorites
I hope you took something away from this video if you guys enjoyed this video
Maybe i'll do a 2025 favorites, but that's quite a time ahead And if you're
watching this before or around the holidays happy holidays to you.
I hope you have a lovely time Thank you for watching again, and I will
see you guys in my next video Love you